We have awaited your
arrival, Wise Prince.
Ministry of Justice
It is truly an honor to meet you.
I am Viny Aussie,
Vice Minister of Justice.
Viny Aussie
Vice Minister of Justice
My number two, eh?
He's young. Still on the rise, I'm sure.
What are my duties?
Explain it to me.
A rough outline will do.
Of course. You have two primary duties.
Meeres Empire
First is the coordination of all
courthouses across the empire.
Our ministry also tries many
cases that occur in the capital.
And, as with the rebellion six years ago,
it is customary for the ministry
or the emperor himself
to judge those who commit serious
crimes such as insurrection.
So in other words, the ministry also
functions as a common courthouse.
That is correct.
Do you try cases, as well?
Depending on the case.
And how much do you receive in bribes?
I-I do no such thing!
I'm not trying to force
you into admitting guilt.
I only want to know the real story.
I'll forget as soon as I leave this room.
Just tell me the truth.
I might have expected as much.
I, personally, do not accept many bribes.
A few hundred rean annually,
I suppose.
I have a rule, you see.
Those beneath me accept at
least ten times that much.
What rule?
I do not accept bribes
in cases of murder.
Why is that?
It is too easily exposed.
If the accuser bears a grudge,
I could become a target for revenge,
leading to irreparable damage.
I accept bribes only in cases that
could easily go in either direction.
Your Highness?
Assuming you take 500 in a year, I'll
give you 5,000, ten times that.
You will not accept bribes while I'm here.
I want to live up to the emperor's
expectations. Please help me do so.
I can see why the emperor gave you
the title of "the Wise" at age six
and appointed you
minister-prince of justice.
I don't need extra money,
and I will stop accepting bribes.
Please allow me to work for Your
Highness from this day forward.
I should be suspicious of
ulterior motives, but...
Name
Noah Ararat  Minister-Prince of Justice
Sex
Male
Level
Fire
Strength
Stamina
Intelligence
I'm counting on you, Viny.
Of course.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
Thank you for arranging this grand
celebration for me, Brother Oscar.
Well, I'm happy, too.
After our brother Henry,
Oscar Ararat
Eighth Prince
you're the second minister-prince in
all of the emperor's fifty-year reign.
Despite how it may seem,
I quite like you.
Let me congratulate you.
You aren't happy?
It isn't that, but why did His Majesty
appoint us as minister-princes?
Probably because you're so dear to him.
I can't completely rule that out.
In Henry's case, he had the legitimate
reason of suppressing the rebellion.
I don't have that kind of record,
so maybe it's natural to conclude that
His Majesty is showing me favoritism.
And yet...
Brother, you're aware the empire nearly
collapsed at one point, are you not?
Yes.
It happened because of the empire's
system of choosing a crown prince to rule.
Because the emperor's successor
is determined at birth,
the princes who were not the crown
prince idled their lives away,
and domestic stability
was drastically shaken.
Thirteenth Prince
Twelfth Prince
Eleventh Prince
Ninth Prince
Eighth Prince
Tenth Prince
Seventh Prince
Imperial Castle
Following introspection, the empire
now grants every prince his own fief,
Sixth Prince
Fifth Prince
Fourth Prince
and ensures they get a proper education.
Third Prince
First Prince
Second Prince
But what does that have to do with this?
Don't you think appointing me minister
goes beyond "an education"?
You can't mean...
he wants to make you crown prince?
I don't know.
If he's merely doting on me,
there's no problem, but...
Your Highness...
Incredible. You were right.
Hmm?
I received a report from
a eunuch I've bought off.
The emperor intends
to name me minister-prince of finance
at tomorrow's morning assembly.
It can't be...
The emperor is making Albert...
At any rate...
today, we're here to celebrate
you and toast your intuition.
Right.
What's this?!
Stop!
I am told that 167 were
arrested, including Keats.
They intended to pressure
Your Majesty into abdicating and,
once you were deposed as emperor, have
the crown prince assume the throne.
They confessed to the very
plot our intel indicated.
He has been crown prince for
thirty years of my fifty-year reign.
I suppose he can wait no longer.
Bear in mind that there is no evidence
of the crown prince's involvement
in this incident.
I am aware. I won't do
anything to Albert.
This Keats man will be executed,
and that will be the end of it.
What became of the incident with Oscar?
I have just sent out a eunuch who
is friends with His Highness.
It would seem His Highness
was aware of the situation.
Oh?
His Highness Noah was with him, as well.
Then it must have been Noah who
caught on to my intentions.
According to the report...
Of course. Remarkable as ever, that Noah.
Gilbert is no good.
Albert is no good.
Who, then? Who is worthy
of succeeding me?
Henry? Oscar? Noah?
Any of them will do as long
as he can overcome my trial.
Episode 7
The Emperor's Wishes
The aforementioned are the leader and
accomplices in the attempted insurrection.
And of course they're all
people close to Albert.
His confidant, his former tutor,
his knights...
Anyone would conclude that this was a
revolt led by the crown prince's faction.
What will you do?
That's the natural reaction.
As for whether Albert had
a hand in this or not...
Under imperial law, if one of the
imperial family commits a crime,
there are provisions that ensure
their penalty is light.
But there is just one exception:
insurrection.
Any member of the imperial family
who is involved in an insurrection
is to be cut in half at the waist,
be they leader or accomplice.
They face the same sentence if
they are aware of the scheme
and fail to report it to the emperor.
Given how many of his
people are involved,
there's no way Albert
didn't know about this.
But...
The crown prince's
insurrection and execution
Emperor
Crown Prince, Second Prince
Albert
Third Prince
Kiro
would be a massive scandal that shakes
the very foundation of the empire.
What has the emperor said?
He said to state the relevant law,
and to punish those involved accordingly.
I see.
I now understand the
emperor's intentions.
I will now pass judgment.
What is it?
I have decided how to
sentence the insurgents.
Proceed.
From among those who were arrested, the
leader will be cut in half at the waist,
and the accomplices will be executed.
The executions will be carried out
as soon as they are sentenced.
The fact that he limited
it only to those arrested
must mean that he currently has no
intention of bringing Albert into this.
That means only those on
the list will be judged.
I could postpone their deaths
until the day of the year when
all executions are carried out.
But Albert's involvement could be revealed,
through a pardon or something similar.
So I must execute them as soon as possible.
This is all within the
bounds of imperial law.
Well done.
Cruz.
Your Majesty.
Noah has done well.
Add a thousand rean to his annual salary.
This is not a feat worthy of a reward.
He really didn't want to
get Albert involved in this.
Brilliant as usual, Noah.
My hopes for you remain high.
Keep up the good work.
Your Highness!
Hey! What happened?
Your... Highness...
Intruders... still... inside...
Hey!
Send for reinforcements!
Ask my brother at the Ministry
of Military Affairs to—
Wait... The timing of this...
No.
Gather our allies!
Let no one inside or outside
the mansion other than me,
even the other princes!
Understood.
Y-Your Highness...
All officials, stand down!
Not good enough!
Damn it!
I won't let you commit suicide.
Hey! We're pulling out!
Impossible!
Your Highness!
I don't believe it...
You defeated them all?
Incredible...
What's the situation?
You can see the casualties
among our guards.
And all the insurgents were killed.
All of them?
They were silenced.
In other words, these are Albert's...
the crown prince's men.
Your Highness?!
Your Highness! What are you...
These four did this to me.
What is the heaviest punishment
for severely wounding a prince?
Execution in all cases,
and by summary judgment.
Then do that immediately!
Of course!
The executions have been carried out.
Good. Now this whole matter is over.
Your Highness never ceases to amaze.
I swear... One misstep and the whole
empire would've been on the rocks.
Damned crown prince.
Pardon me.
Sorry to summon you here.
You are wounded, no less.
There's no need for formality.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I could not be more
ashamed at my failure.
No matter. You are not solely to blame.
Still, to think they wounded
a man of your caliber.
Were they truly so capable?
I figured he would ask that.
Given his intelligence network,
he probably already knows that
I gave myself this wound.
I believe that strength...
is not solely dependent on
one's skill with the sword.
No matter how talented one is,
he can falter if his mental
fragility is taken advantage of.
I see. Truly, I have a fine son...
no, a son I would be proud
to present to all.
It appears he understands the amount
of thought I put into handling that.
I only wish all my sons were like you.
Can you walk with me?
Did you know, Noah,
among emperors who come
to be known as great leaders,
nine out of ten tarnish their
reputation later in life.
Is he talking about the
crown prince's insurrection?
Our emperor led this nation into a golden
age like none it had known before.
He will most certainly be described
as a great leader in history books.
But if that insurrection
had been successful,
they would say he grew
senile in his old age
and couldn't even control his own sons.
Clearly, the emperor no longer
trusts the crown prince.
The reason he won't do
anything about it now
is because the very act of
forsaking the crown prince
would tarnish his reputation
in his later years.
Your Majesty, if I may,
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
You appointed Henry, Oscar,
and myself minister-princes,
but as that in itself is a first,
I fear some aspects of it will be handled
poorly somewhere down the line.
So I would appreciate it if you could
appoint someone to coordinate all of us.
Are you asking for my
first prime minister?
No, as an example, you could appoint
someone above the three of us
to bring order to all that we do.
Prime Minister-Prince
I am proposing the establishment of a new
role known as the prime minister-prince.
And I would like His Highness the
Crown Prince to fill that role.
Impossible.
Your wounds aren't healed yet.
Leave for today.
A crown prince of thirty years...
I can understand why my brother
would begin to feel impatient.
In which case...
Your Majesty would still have
the final say in all decisions.
Emperor
You need only allow him to emulate you.
Prime Minister-Prince
But he would still rank above
the ministers, would he not?
What if the prime minister
dismisses an important matter
Minister-Prince
of Finance
of Justice
Minister-Prince
of Military Affairs
Prime Minister-Prince
and it never reaches me at all?
(Final Say)
Emperor
To prevent that,
each minister-prince will have the
right to file a direct appeal.
Minister-Prince
of Finance
of Justice
Minister-Prince
of Military Affairs
Prime Minister-Prince
If all of us feel equally
strongly about the matter,
we can bypass the prime minister
and appeal directly to you.
(Can Directly
Appeal)
(Final Say)
Emperor
That prevents the crown prince
from holding any actual power.
It doesn't matter if the prime
minister-prince's role has any substance.
It will be no more than a title.
Remarkable.
You are right. If that will
work, it is the best choice.
Thank you for your counsel, Noah.
Consider it delivered to the throne.
I am most grateful.
It truly is a shame you
weren't born sooner.
He understood my proposal instantly.
He is truly worthy of being
called a great leader.
Preventing the tarnishing of
his reputation in his old age
will be the best way to ensure his
people can live peaceful lives.
I must reward you.
Money is not a sufficient
reward for such a proposal.
Cruz.
Your Majesty.
We're going to the vault.
It was by your own judgment that
you discovered that ring, correct?
Yes.
I wish to see that judgment in action.
Choose any one item you like.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Search, Leviathan.
This one?
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu